[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "Did you have a 13-year affair with this woman?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "Did you know her for 13 years?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Did you have a 13-year affair with this woman?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Did you know her for 13 years?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Wolf, an extraordinary twist today because you weren't expecting him to come out with that until halfway through your interview, is that right?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "No, it was not.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Was this an affair?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "There was no sex?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "None?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "It was very strange because Lynn Wood who is a prominent lawyer in Atlanta, he's well known to a lot of TV viewers out there.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "What do you make of all this, Wolf?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "The question is, I guess, can she prove it was inappropriate?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you remember the Anthony Weiner case.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Because if it turns out that he is lying about this affair, you would have to imagine that would be the end of his campaign, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, certainly if these allegations by Miss White are true, then it certainly goes to the issue of the character and the honesty of Herman Cain.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "What do you make of today's new revelations involving Herman Cain?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Now apparently she has quite a bit of corroboration in the form of at least numerous texts, perhaps e-mails, perhaps other evidence from Herman Cain.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "I mean, is it really credible that a woman would make a charge of a 13-year affair if there was simply no truth at all to it?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Not with my client, but I do feel that she is extremely credible and her corroborating witness, one of them, Dr. Zuckerman, the pediatrician, came forward.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "In light of what's come out today, Gloria, are you planning any further action with your client?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "It seems new.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Is this new or does it just seem new?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I think, frankly, that Obama's biggest opponent is the economy.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Who do you think right now Barack Obama would least want to face?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "You'd think so.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Is he terminally shot below the bows now, do you think, in terms of this ongoing series of scandals about his private life?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "I think most people don't know who he is.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Why does he not get more attention?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "The new name that you just gave me.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "I like the Big Shaqtus, but which one of those do you particularly like?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "The big duke.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "It felt right.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "I know it wasn't probably the perfect scripted ending, but do you feel inside you it's the time to go on?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "'NEAL: No, not at all.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Taking up golf yet?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, you used the wrong choice of words.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "With 10 percent of people in this country unemployed, I was like, what are they up to, these guys?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "You know he's the president, and you know, I come from a military background.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What do you think of Obama?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "I would say less.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Do you think that having the first African- American president has made America more or less racist?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I'm not sure.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "When you've worked your way up from nothing to be what you are, what has happened to stop that kind of thing happening?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "How to expand beyond the sport?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "It's very awful.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "But it's pretty awful, isn't it, what's been going on?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "And I'm glad you understood that.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "I mean, unless I'm mistaken, it wasn't that you hated him, you just both wanted to be top dog, right?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "I'll have to go with Michael Jordan.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Who is the best player you've ever seen?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "'NEAL: He knows -- yes, that man right there.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "What I've always wondered about you is, do you ever go out and people pick a fight with you?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Well, maybe a little bit.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "More to do with the fact that you're seven foot tall and could pummel them to pieces?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "All of it.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "When you look back on it, with the exception of the births of your kids and marriage and so on, what is being the one moment you would relive again, that's been the greatest moment?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "It is getting better.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "It's getting better, my accent?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I've been blessed.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "How do you feel about still being around?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you take the drugs twice a day, but I work out every day, too.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "In terms of the medication you had to take every day and so -- how do you keep as healthy as you clearly appear to be?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I think to continue to help people understand this disease hasn't gone anywhere.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "It's the World AIDS Day on December 1st, what is the overriding message you would like to communicate on this particular anniversary?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you know, dealing with Shaq, Shaq is so amazing.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Do you wish you'd carried on?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Well, I think that I was more shocked that the people who did support me.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Or were you more disappointed by those you thought would who didn't?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "I'm still mad today about that.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "That must have really annoyed you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "No question about it.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "And if you're playing in a team, a small team of people, and you're both touted by different sets of fans to be number one in the game, there's going to be a rivalry, isn't there?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Well, Michael Jordan was the best, and -- hands down.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Who's the best you've ever seen?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Well, he's the one I would love to play with.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "I would imagine that you walk out and you got Shaq O'Neal bearing down on you, there can't be many worse moments in sports, are there?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Well, I think when we look back at it, we wish it didn't happen from both the owners side and the players side.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Did it ever happen at al in the current climate?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "1987, the hook shot versus the Celtics.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "What is the one basket you scored that if I could give you a minute of your life back, you'd do it again?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "All the time.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "How often do you think about it?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "Not every day, but all the time.", "docId": "111128pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Every day?", "qSentId": 638}]